var questions = [{
    question: "How do you alter the value of the text element in a span tag?",
    option1: "Compact document.getElementById(spanId).firstChild; Sheet",
    option2: "document.getElementById(radioButtonId).value; Screen Sheet",
    option3: "document.getElementById(id);le Sheet",
    option4: "document.getElementById(spanId).firstChild.nodeValue = New Value",
    answer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: "For checkboxes, how do you get the text value of the control?",
    option1: "document.getElementById(radioButtonId).checked = true; //Could also be false",
    option2: "document.getElementById(CheckboxId).checked = true; //Could also be false",
    option3: "document.getElementById(radioButtonId).value;",
    option4: "document.getElementById(TextBoxId).focus;",
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "For radio buttons, how do you set the current checked status of the control?",
    option1: "<style>",
    option2: "<css>",
    option3: "<script>",
    option4: "<js>",
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "What Math object method is used to return a random number?",
    option1: "Math.random()",
    option2: "If data types don't match they fail comparison",
    option3: "(Condition_Expression)? Value_If_True : Value_If_False",
    option4: "Math.floor(number)",
    answer: "1"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the identity operator for equals?",
    option1: "//",
    option2: "!==",
    option3: "=",
    option4: "====",
    answer: "3"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you code a for statement in JavaScript?",
    option1: "<window.onload = function()>",
    option2: "<document.getElementById(id);>",
    option3: "<for (counter; condition; incrementor) {}>",
    option4: "<var stringVar = part 1 + part 2>",
    answer: "3"
  },  {
    question: "What is the string escape sequence to insert a vertical tab in JavaScript?",
    option1: "toTimeString()",
    option2: "\\",
    option3: "===",
    option4: "\v",
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of a return statement in a function?",
    option1: "Returns the value and continues executing rest of the statements, if any",
    option2: "Returns the value and stops the program",
    option3: "Returns the value and stops executing the function",
    option4: "Stops executing the function and returns value",
    answer: "3"
  },
  {
    question: "What are the two methods common to most controls?",
    option1: "Type, Src",
    option2: "focus //Brings focus to the control blur //Removes focus from the control",
    option3: "form, Max_Value",
    option4: "Min_Value",
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you view the current web address using JavaScript?",
    option1: "window.location()",
    option2: ":",
    option3: "//",
    option4: "document.getElementByld(id)",
    answer: "3"
  }
];
